

SASHKO KRSTEVSKI

Profile

Experienced and professional IT Administrator with over ten years of valuable experience. Familiar and adept in working with engineering, industrial engineering, change management. Accustomed to handling IT support and supporting various engineering departments with IT tools and applications. Bringing forth a motivated attitude and the ability to establish strong and productive relationships with other company members.

Employment History

IT Manager at Sinceritas AD, Skopje

September 2021 — Present

- Supervising daily operations of network and server infrastructure
- Aligning IT infrastructure with current and future business requirements and goals
- Managing IT budgets, forecast, handling cash flow and enforcing cost-effectiveness
- Assuring that IT activities are within the limits of applicable laws, codes and regulations
- Testing, troubleshooting and adjusting information systems to operate effectively
- Implementing security of the network, data and its storage and communication systems
- Organized and prioritized work to complete assignments in a timely, efficient manner

IT Administrator at Draexlmaier North Macedonia, Kavadarci

August 2012 — August 2021

- Develop, supervise and maintain IT infrastructure
- Create and provide solutions for complex problems
- · First level support for production and office systems

System engineer at Faculty of computer science and engineering at the "St Cyril and Methodious" University in Skopje, Skopje

August 2011 — August 2012

- Develop, supervise and maintain IT infrastructure
- Develop, supervise and maintain VMware environment

System engineer at Institute of Informatics at the Faculty of Natural Sciences and Mathematics at the "St Cyril and Methodious" University in Skopje, Skopje

January 2010 — August 2011

- Develop, supervise and maintain IT infrastructure
- Develop, supervise and maintain VMware servers

Details

Str. Dime Turimandjov br.18 Kavadarci, 1430 North Macedonia +38971219782 sasko.krstevski@hotmail.com

Date of birth 18.06.1982

Nationality
Macedonian

Driving license Category B

Links

Linkedin

Skills

Microsoft Server 2019

Windows Server 2012 R2

Microsoft SQL Server

Office365

C#

SQL

Java

ASP.NET

HTML & CSS

JavaScript

VMware

Microsoft Dynamics 365 Finance and Operations

Languages

English

Serbian

System engineer, WEB Administrator at National and University Library "St. Kliment Ohridski" - Skopje, Skopje

January 2010 — August 2012

- Develop, supervise and maintain IT infrastructure
- Develop, supervise and maintain VMware servers
- Install and maintain WEB servers
- Develop and maintain WEB pages

Education

System Engineering, Institute of Informatics at the Faculty of Natural Sciences and Mathematics at the "St Cyril and Methodious" University in Skopje, Skopje

October 2001 — December 2009

Natural sciences and mathematic, High School "Dobri Daskalov - Kavadarci, Kavadarci

September 1997 — June 2001

Courses

Microsoft Windows Server 2012, Semos Education

Microsoft SQL Server® 2014, Semos Education

Business App Developer, Axapta Learning Center